const STORE = {
    questions: [
      {//1
        question: "Which mutant character has adamantium claws and skeleton?",
        options: [
          "A. Colossus",
          "B. Sabertooth",
          "C. Wolverine",
          "D. Gambit"
        ],
        answer: "C. Wolverine"
      },
      //2
      {
        question: "Which mutant character can control the weather?",
        options: [
          "A. Rogue",
          "B. Jean Grey",
          "C. Jubilee",
          "D. Storm"
        ],
        answer: "D. Storm"
      },
      //3
      {
        question: "Which mutant character has psionic and telepathic powers?",
        options: [
          "A. Cyclops",
          "B. Bishop",
          "C. Cable",
          "D. Charles Xavier"
        ],
        answer: "D. Charles Xavier"
      },
      //4
      {
        question: "Which mutant character later turns into the Phoenix?",
        options: [
          "A. Jean Grey",
          "B. Jubilee",
          "C. Rogue",
          "D. Kitty Pride"
        ],
        answer: "A. Jean Grey"
      },
      //5
      {
        question: "Which mutant character has a Ph.D in Biophysics and Genetics?",
        options: [
          "A. Colossus",
          "B. Cyclops",
          "C. Bishop",
          "D. Beast"
        ],
        answer: "D. Beast"
      },
      //6
      {
        question: "Which mutant character fires optic blasts from his eyes?",
        options: [
          "A. Cable",
          "B. Bishop",
          "C. Cyclops",
          "D. Wolverine"
        ],
        answer: "C. Cyclops"
      },
      //7
      {
        question: "Which mutant character claims he's from the future?",
        options: [
          "A. Magneto",
          "B. Charles Xavier",
          "C. Bishop",
          "D. Forge"
        ],
        answer: "C. Bishop"
      },
      //8
      {
        question: "Which mutant character time travels to prevent an 'Apocalypse'?",
        options: [
          "A. Charles Xavier",
          "B. Nightcrawler",
          "C. Cable",
          "D. Archangel"
        ],
        answer: "C. Cable"
      },
      //9
      {
        question: "Which mutant character is a ninja with telekinetic powers?",
        options: [
          "A. Kitty Pride",
          "B. Rogue",
          "C. Psylocke",
          "D. Jubilee"
        ], 
        answer: "C. Psylocke"
      },
      //10
      {
        question: "Which mutant character has a German accent and can teleport?",
        options: [
          "A. Beast",
          "B. Wolverine",
          "C. Colossus",
          "D. Nightcrawler"
        ],
        answer: "D. Nightcrawler"
      }
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0
};